dress4less.com 2012-11-16

# Privacy Policy for Dress 4 Less

## Privacy Policy

**Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information.**

Thank you for visiting Dress4less.com. This notice explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information. 

OUR ONLINE INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE PRACTICES MAY DIFFER FROM OUR PRACTICES REGARDING INFORMATION OBTAINED OFFLINE. 

REMEMBER IF YOU REGISTER WITH DRESS4LESS.COM, PARTICIPATE IN A SURVEY, PURCHASE SOMETHING THROUGH THE WEBSITE, ENTER ANY OF OUR CONTESTS OR PROMOTIONS, YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS. AS WE UPDATE AND EXPAND OUR SERVICES, THIS POLICY MIGHT CHANGE, SO CHECK IT OUT FROM TIME TO TIME. 

**The Information We Collect.**

At Dress4less.com you can do a variety of things! You may be able to order products, enter contests, participate in surveys, vote in polls, subscribe to a service (like our newsletter) or participate in a chat room. The types of personally identifiable information (i.e. information that can directly identify you or indicate where you might be contacted) that may be collected at these pages includes: name, address, age, date of birth, sex, grade level, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services. You can view or change your information at any time. [Click here](http://www.dress4less.com/login.php) to edit your profile or [click here](http://www.dress4less.com/contact-us.php) to email us. 

Sometimes you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to a friend, you might submit the friend's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages may include: recipient's name, address, age, date of birth, grade level, e-mail address, sex and telephone number. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e. generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online or Earthlink). 

**How We Use and Disclose the Information.**

We will use the personal information you provide online for the purpose(s) you have submitted. Examples of us using your personal information for the purpose(s) submitted include if you order a catalog, we will send to you a catalog in the mail or, if you have won a contest, sending to you an email notification that you have won. In addition, we may send to you an e-mail offering products or services which we think you may be interested in or to ask you to participate in a survey. For example, we may send to you an e-mail regarding special merchandise offers and announcements about products or services we offer. We may also contact you offline. For example, when you provide your mailing address, we may send to you in the mail special offers, promotions and catalogs, which we think may be of interest to you. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please go to Edit My Profile at DRESS4LESS.COM or [click here](http://www.dress4less.com/contact-us.php) to email us. 

**How We Share Your Personal Information.**

We will not share the personal information you provide except (a) if it is for the purpose(s) you provided it (which might include providing your information to an affiliated company or a third party); (b) with your consent; (c) as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company or others from injury (e.g. in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request or when we believe that someone is causing (or about to cause) injury to or interference with the rights or property of another); (d) with other persons or companies with whom we contract to carry out internal site operations or our business activities (for example, sending out a product or a promotional item that you have requested on the site); and/or (e) notifying you when we make changes to one of our subscriber agreements or this policy. 

Examples of us sharing your personal information for the purposes submitted are if you request information regarding financial aid, we may provide the information provided to a third party lender so that they can send to you directly the information you requested or if you enter a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by a third party, we may forward your information to such third party. 

We will seek to obtain your consent at the place where the information is collected either by an "opt-in" or "opt-out" method, or by other means (such as sending to you an e-mail). 

Additionally, with your consent, we may share certain of the personal information you provide online with companies not affiliated with us (i.e. third party companies) who are interested in marketing their products or services to you or in asking you questions, both online and offline. Such companies may include consumer products, telecom, financial, military, market research, entertainment, and educational services companies and their third party service providers. If you want us to stop sharing your personal information with these companies, please go to Edit My Profile at DRESS4LESS.COM or [click here](http://www.dress4less.com/contact-us.php) to email us. If you consent to receiving communications from non-affiliated companies, you may need to communicate with them directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications or if you wish to change any data you provided online. In this instance, any changes or amendments to your personal information must be given directly to each company who communicates with you as these changes, amendments and/or deletions may not be exchanged between us and non-affiliated companies. 

If we do share personal information to a non-affiliated company, to the extent practical, we require that they protect such information in a manner that is consistent with this policy. We cannot, however, guarantee how these non-affiliated companies will use your personal information. 

**Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information.**

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how our site is used, as well as to offer you products, programs or services. Sometimes we share aggregate information with others, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies. 

**Collection of Information by Others.**

Our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should check the other sites' privacy notices since we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by them. 

We may offer e-mail services, contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with non-affiliated companies. Based on our agreement with them, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that site visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. We have no control over the use of this information by these companies. 

**Cookies.**

To enhance your online experience with us, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files placed on your hard disk by our web server to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to provide the personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. 

We use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, to understand how our site is used, and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services. You can opt to have your browser reject cookies. If you do that, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our site in order to participate in certain promotions and other stuff. You should also know that companies that advertise on our web site (and their agents) might use their own cookies. This policy does not cover how these companies use their cookies. 

**Clickstream Data.**

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data," can be collected and stored by a web site's server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to Dress4less.com. We may use clickstream data to help enhance your experience on our site, including making recommendations we believe may be of interest to you. We may also use clickstream data as a form of non-personally identifiable information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of Dress4less.com, how visitors navigate throughout the site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will only be used to improve our site. 

**Supplementing Information.**

From time to time we may supplement information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address. Thus, information we obtain through Dress4less.com may be intermingled with and used in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than Dress4less.com, including both offline and online sources. 

**Discussions and Community Tools.**

We may, from time to time, make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups and other community tools available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information for other users to view and for us to use. For example, from time to time, we may use the content you write (including your name or screen name if you post it) for promotional purposes, in e-mail newsletters or elsewhere, and by using Dress4less.com and/or these chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups, and other community tools, you agree that we may do so. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas, since anyone - not just us - may use publicly posted information. 

**Our Commitment to Security.**

We believe we have in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online as well as offline. When your personal information is passed onto non-affiliated companies, to the extent practical, we require that they also have in place the appropriate safeguards. We cannot, however, guarantee that they do so. 

**International Users.**

If you are visiting Dress4less.com from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, your orders placed through Dress4less.com will be fully processed in and shipped from the United States and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using Dress4less.com, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. This policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of the State of New York and the USA, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the USA in the State of New York. 

** **

**"Phishing" and e-mail scams.**

If you receive an e-mail that appears to be from us but is asking you for your personal information (for example your credit card details), please do not respond. We simply do not request your credit card information, user name, password or any other personal information by e-mail. Such e-mails are a “phishing” scam in which scammers send e-mails impersonating legitimate businesses, companies or services in an attempt to gain your personal information.

 **How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information.**

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you online, or how to correct any errors in such information, please go to Edit My Profile at DRESS4LESS.COM or [click here](http://www.dress4less.com/contact-us.php) to email us. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**About Children - Kids under 13**

Dress4Less is not directed to children under the age of 13. Our website does not accept registration by and we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13. We have taken commercially reasonable steps to restrict use of this site to those who are at least 13 years old. We do not sell products for purchase by children and all children's products we sell are for purchase by adults only, or with adult permission 

**Special Note for Parents.**

If you have concerns about this site or its services, wish to find out if your child is a member or has registered for one our services, or wish to cancel your child's membership, please [click here](http://www.dress4less.com/contact-us.php) to email us. If you believe that your child under 13 has gained access to our site without your permission, you may [click here](http://www.dress4less.com/contact-us.php) to email us. 

**Transfer of Business Assets.**

The personal information you provide is considered a company asset and may be included among our transferred assets and the assets of any or all of our subsidiaries or affiliates if any of their assets is ever acquired by a third party. 

**Changes to this Policy.**

If you choose to visit Dress4less.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. If you have any concern about privacy at Dress4less.com, please [click here](http://www.dress4less.com/contact-us.php) to email us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our privacy policy and the Terms of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you. 

This policy is effective as of September 25, 2009. 

**How to Contact Us.**

The information you provide pursuant to this privacy policy is owned by The Sy Group. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may [click here](http://www.dress4less.com/contact-us.php) to email us or contact us as follows:   
**  
The Sy Group, LLC.  
8058 Lubec Street   
Downey, CA 90240   
Attn: Privacy   
Telephone: 1-800-518-9766**

 **  
**
